©
© P @ rM ! NdeR
© P @ rM ! NdeR M @ nkÖÖ
© P @ rM ! NdeR M @ nkÖÖ ™
© P @ rM ! NdeR M @ nkÖÖ ™ Mobile - + 919815899536
( BREATH TREMBLING )
( DOOR CREAKING )
( WHIMPERING )
Kaylie !
Shh !
( GUNSHOT )
And I fired .
As many times as I 've had this dream ...
it 's never been me before .
Holding the gun .
I know .
That 's very good .
It implies a true , deeply-rooted acceptance of responsibility .
And it tells me that you haven 't only overcome your delusion
in your conscious mind ...
but in his subconscious mind as well .
It 's my opinion that Tim is a healthy adult
who represents no danger to himself or anyone else .
And I believe he should be discharged , as the state requested ,
on his upcoming 21st birthday .
( FOOTSTEPS )
WOMAN : going once ...
eleven-five twice ...
- ( GAVEL BANGS ) - Sold to the gentleman .
Congratulations to you , sir .
That 's bidder number 131 .
All right , and our next item for bid
is a gorgeous antique mirror , recovered from the Levesque Estate .
The Lasser Glass is a well-traveled gem .
It spent several seasons adorning the walls at Balmoral Castle ,
Scottish home of the Royal Family .
This is the original glass and the original frame .
The mirror is in remarkable condition , save for a small hairline fracture
down in the lower right-hand corner .
The frame is carved out of one piece of Bavarian Black Cedar .
And we will go ahead and start the bidding
at a conservative ten thousand dollars .
Do I have ten ? Right here in front . Thank you , sir .
DOCTOR : Your sister is picking you up , then ?
Her message even said something about helping me find a job .
That 'd be wonderful for your transition .
AUCTIONEER : We 're at 12,000 dollars on the phone ...
You sure you don 't want me to come with you ?
Some moral support ?
No . But thank you .
I think I better do this part myself .
- Wait up for us . - Of course .
Remember what we talked about .
You 've had a support system , a mandated support system ,
to help you get well .
Kaylie had to get by on her own .
It 's very important that you reconnect with your sister .
But it 's more important that you protect your recovery .
Sixteen thousand .
Sixteen thousand on Skype .
That is sixteen , going once .
Sixteen twice .
Sold . Please pass along our congratulations .
- See you tonight . - OK .
( DOOR BUZZES )
Son , just pull the door when it buzzes .
Hey , little brother .
Your half of the estate .
Oh , apartments .
So all the studies say that you should transition
to a place that isn 't necessarily large ,
so I printed off some listings for studios .
But in the meantime , until you find one you like ,
we would love it if you stayed with us .
Kaylie , I don 't know how to thank you .
Well , I wanted to talk to you about all of this sooner .
But suddenly they wouldn 't let me in to see you .
It wasn 't ...
It wasn 't that they wouldn 't let you in to see me .
I just had some things I needed to figure out for myself .
I get it .
I 'm your family .
The only thing that matters is that you 're here now .
( WHISPERING ) I found it .
- What do you mean ? - You know .
It wasn 't easy .
I tracked it down mostly through second bidders ,
people who lost at the auctions .
It was in storage , part of an estate collection in Bremen .
It took me a year and a half to get it into our warehouse
and it lasted less than a week .
It 's about to ship out to a new buyer , so we only have a few days ,
but it should be enough .
A few days for what , Kaylie ?
To keep our promise .
And kill it .
( DOG BARKING )
OK , guys , the couch can go there .
And those boxes are kitchen .
Bam ! Bam !
Tim , we don 't shoot the movers .
And as soon as I get my files organized , you will have them .
- ( PHONE BUZZING ) - Yes . Shoot .
Can I call you back ?
Jeff , I am so sorry I didn 't return your call .
I 've just been slammed .
It 's a lot easier when you have a staff .
Kaylie 's under arrest .
She 's not here , buddy .
- ( TOY GUN FIRING ) - Sneak attack !
You are so dead !
Honey ?
And this goes ?
OK , against the wall .
Watch the molding .
Thank you . OK .
OK . It 's fragile .
( KIDS CHATTERING )
- Hey , guys ! Take it outside . - But , Mom ...
The alternative is moving boxes .
GIRL : Oh , come on . Come on .
So we 'll talk soon . OK .
WOMAN : Thanks , guys . OK .
I 'll be right out .
So you expanded the furniture order ?
I don 't know if I 'm loving this desk here .
Were you gonna tell me or just wait till I saw the Visa bill ?
Hold on .
I was hoping to smooth that over with a three-piece vanity set ..
.. that is supposed to be here ... Is it not here ?
( LAUGHING )
I get it . OK . Do your office however you want .
- Thank you . - Mm-hm .
It 's a bit ostentatious , though , don 't you think ?
I 'm confused , because you wanted the antiques .
And I said I was fine with IKEA .
Yeah , I wanted to get a few pieces to upgrade the place ,
not turn it into a showroom .
Listen , we got a new home , a new company ,
so we get new furniture . Makes sense .
Same old wife , though , right ?
Well , I told you I was fine with IKEA .
- Kidding . - I 'm not IKEA .
( SIGHS ) You sure you prefer this ?
Our guest room is a lot nicer than this .
Yeah . I think it might be best .
My own space .
You promised me you 'd never forget what really happened .
You promised .
I was ten years old .
Well ...
I 'm doing it tomorrow night .
And ... I could really , really use your help .
Good night , Tim .
I feel like my scar is more noticeable now than it was ten years ago .
Let me take a look .
I 'm a professional .
( GASPS )
( KISSING ) What scar ?
( CHUCKLING )
We 're nowhere near done .
So ?
You 've only put together the bed .
That wasn 't easy .
( KISSING CONTINUES )
( SIGHS )
( FOOT BANGING )
( GRUNTING )
Damn it .
Shit .
( DOG BARKING )
( GASPS , CHOKING )
No ! No ! No !
( SCREAMING ) No ! No ! No !
It 's OK . It 's OK . It 's OK .
( SOBBING )
- ( PANTING )
- It 's OK . It 's OK .
It 's just one of your night terrors .
It 's OK . Shh ...
- Shh ... - ( BREATHING SLOWS )
( KNOCKING )
- Hey . - Hey .
So I requisitioned you your own printer .
You don 't have to share anymore .
- We 'll take you off the network . - OK .
Because I guess there were some complaints about people
printing out their sales reports and finding some really ...
graphic crime scene photos from , uh ...
your computer .
I noticed you put in a transfer order for the Lasser Glass .
- Yeah , as a repair . - Oh .
I thought Warren said no repairs .
He changed his mind .
Got to be honest , I 'm really just waiting for an explanation
for the corpse print-outs .
I know things have been strange at times .
And you know I 'm dealing with some dark stuff ,
some parental stuff , with Tim out .
I 'll never expect you to understand that part of my life .
Just bear with me a day or two more .
Things will get back to normal .
I promise .
I don 't usually get transfer orders to third-party repair houses .
Oh , yeah , the buyer wants his guy to look at it before it ships .
But we both know you 'd do it better .
No argument there .
I 'll take it there myself .
Babysit it every step of the way .
Better get some furni pads if we 're going to move her .
Hello again .
You must be hungry .
I hope this still hurts .
( INHALING QUIETLY )
- You 're all set . - ( GASPING )
You all right ?
I 'm great .
The guys will wrap her up for you in a bit .
Thank you , Warren .
I 'll see you at home .
- ( CELL PHONE RINGING )
- My car is by the loading dock .
- Hello . - TIM : Hey .
- Got a phone . - Cool .
You just need to sign the order .
I don 't feel good about the way we left it last night .
Can we meet up somewhere and talk ?
Of course . Can you come by the house ?
Sure . What 's your address ?
No . The house .
Yes , I have it in front of me .
I don 't know , probably half an hour .
Does that work ?
OK .
Speak then .
( INDISTINCT OVERLAPPING WHISPERS )
( RUSTLING )
( TOY GUN FIRING )
Oh , crap .
I 'm gonna get you , you little brat !
( FIRING CONTINUES )
The answer is still no .
Oh , my God , Ally has one and Maddie has one .
I 'm the only kid in my class without a phone .
That is terrible .
Thanks for nothing , Marie .
( LAUGHING ) Oh !
I 'm going to run out and get one for you right now , daughter ,
love of my life , fruit of my loins .
Well , I wish I 'd been a pineapple .
Hey kids , do me a favor and don 't ever chew your nails like your father .
- It 's gross . - KAYLIE : Hey , Dad ?
OK ... He 's Dad . I 'm Marie .
Who was that lady in your office today ?
Yeah , Dad , who was that lady in your office today ?
What lady ?
I don 't know . Just some lady .
I don 't know .
( DOOR OPENING )
It looks so small .
- Go on , Dog . - You named your dog , Dog ?
No . He doesn 't have a name .
Are you OK ?
Oh , of course .
You haven 't been here since ...
Why don 't you look around ?
( CHAIN RATTLING )
KAYLIE : The house just sat on the market while I was in the foster system .
Released to me when I turned 18 .
I was the only homeowner in the freshman dorms when I started school .
I 'm thinking we should try and sell it , though .
You know , after .
So will you help me with something before you go ?
How the hell did you expect to get this thing in here yourself ?
To be honest , I didn 't .
I always thought it 'd be both of us .
Over here for now .
OK .
( PANTING )
What 's that ?
Yacht anchor . Kill switch .
So , uh ... ( CLEARS THROAT )
I understand if you don 't want to stay .
I accept that , but I got to get started .
I 'll stay for a little bit .
Excuse me .
( CAMERAS BEEPING )
( EXHALES ) Hello .
My name is Kaylie Ann Russell .
I 'm 23 years old .
I 'm with my brother , Timothy Alan Russell .
Alan , of course , after his father .
He 's ...
He 's 21 years old .
It 's 4 : 15pm on October 13th ,
and we are at 2705 Hawthorne Way .
I 'll begin by detailing my precautions before I place and uncover the glass .
There are three cameras , each on its own independent power circuit ,
so if any anomalies occur , there can be a lucid , objective record .
I have private land lines for today 's experiment , along with my cell phone .
And I will now ask my brother for his phone ,
so that I can control all electronic devices .
I just got this , you know .
Thanks , Timbo .
This alarm is set to go off every 45 minutes
to remind me to change the tapes in the cameras .
This alarm is set to go off hourly to remind us to eat .
And we 're fully stocked on water to prevent dehydration .
Now , as for the house itself ...
each room is fitted with its own thermostat ,
from which data is collected by software designed to track and record
temperature fluctuations in hospitals .
Any temperature changes greater than five degrees in either direction
will set off an alarm .
A third precaution is also in place ,
but I 'll get into that in a few more minutes .
So ...
The purpose of today 's experiment
is to prove that the object behind me , the Lasser Glass ,
is home to an observable , predictable supernatural force .
There 's no scientific equivalent for the word " haunted , "
so we 'll just say this object is responsible for at least 45 deaths
in the four centuries of its recorded existence ...
Can I just stop you for a second ?
Don 't ever turn off a camera .
Sorry .
The origin of the Lasser Glass is unknown ,
so I can 't provide a complete history ,
but the trail starts in London in 1754 .
Philip Lasser , the 17th Earl of Leicester ,
acquired the mirror and hung it over his fireplace , and ...
- ( CELL PHONE RINGING )
- Another precaution .
Hi , sweetie . How are you ?
Well , I 'm checking in , uh , as requested .
You all right ?
Everything 's fine .
I know this is silly to ask , but could you try to call on the hour ?
It 's about seven past .
- Uh ... Sure . - I 'll talk to you in 53 minutes .
And I love you .
I 'm expecting regular calls from my fiance , Michael Dumont .
I told him I 'm nervous to be spending time with my recently
un-incarcerated brother , with instructions ...
- to notify the authorities immediately - Wow .
if I do not answer the phone .
- In the room . - Nothing personal .
So , in 1755 , Philip Lasser was found in their grand fireplace .
Burned beyond recognition . While his estate was dismantled
and scattered throughout southern England ,
one of the family 's stewards claimed to see Philip reflected in the mirror .
An allegation apparently taken seriously enough to warrant
a Church investigation into the house .
The glass , thereafter known as the Lasser Glass ,
is sold in public auction in 1758 .
The next known owner is an American rail road tycoon ,
named Robert Clancy , 1864 .
Clancy apparently weighed over 300 pounds .
In fact , while attending university in Connecticut ,
he was known as the South Windham Whale .
He hung the glass in his ballroom in Atlanta .
Later that year , Robert Clancy is photographed
by a local newspaper and , uh ...
Well , he 's dropped a few pounds .
His obit was printed a few weeks later .
Doesn 't list a cause of death .
Unfortunately , he and his estate and the glass
are presumably destroyed in Sherman 's march to the ocean in 1865 .
And after that , the glass is lost .
Until it resurfaces in turn-of-the-century New England .
The next case of note is Mary O 'Connor , 1904 .
She hung the mirror in her private bathroom .
Two weeks later , her niece Beatrice finds Mary dead in the bathtub .
Now , the official coroner 's report lists the cause of death as , get this ...
dehydration .
The woman died of thirst while soaking in a full tub for three days .
The next case of note is Alice Carden in Lake Geneva , Wisconsin , 1943 .
Neighbors reported hearing screams and loud bangs from the house .
The police found the children drowned in a locked cistern .
Alice herself was in the nursery ,
and both of her legs are completely shattered .
Her left arm is broken in four places , and six of her ribs are crushed .
In her right hand is a large hammer she 's been using to break her own bones .
They find her just as she 's going to work on her skull .
Her right arm , though , is completely unharmed .
Because she needed it . To wield the hammer .
Alice later says she believed she was tucking the children into their beds
as she sealed them into the cistern .
She never recovers from her injuries .
And , oh , the family kept several dogs at the farm ,
including an Australian shepherd for the children .
©
© P @ rM ! NdeR
© P @ rM ! NdeR M @ nkÖÖ
( TIMER BUZZING )
Let 's eat .
Who exactly are you talking to ?
On those tapes ?
All the people who stared , pointed .
The kids at school who always found out .
I guess I 'm talking to everyone who ever called Dad a murderer .
Called you a murderer .
Look , Kaylie , we were just kids .
We made up a scary story so we wouldn 't have to accept the fact
that our father was a murderer . He was .
He was a sick man who tortured and killed our ...
You can call me crazy all you like .
But you 're not allowed to talk about him that way .
Tobin Capp , 1955 . Starved to death in his own bedroom .
The mirror was hung over his dresser .
He had a pet Dalmatian .
1965 , California .
The mirror hangs in the lobby of the Hill Trust Bank in San Diego .
A ten-year teller , Marcia Wicker , locks her manager in the bank vault
and then chews through a live power line .
- 1975 , Marisol Chavez ... - Kaylie ...
dies in her bedroom of hemorrhaging due to a miscarriage .
In her nightstand , they find every single one of her teeth
in a little plastic bag and a pair of bloody pliers .
- 2002 ... - There 's a huge difference
between causation and correlation .
I know the difference , thank you .
OK then . In 2001 , Mom and Dad bought that new couch .
Same year , Grandpa had a heart attack , Robbie Schultz got hit by a car .
And our cat ran away .
How much of that do you blame on that couch ?
Can I get back to this now ?
Sure , but let 's get to it , Kaylie .
Let 's talk about why we 're really here .
( WHISPERS ) Let 's .
2002 .
The Lasser Glass adorns the home office of Alan Russell .
Software designer .
Husband to Marie .
Father to Timothy and Kaylie .
Within two weeks of its arrival ,
Marie suffers an intense psychological breakdown
and is tortured and murdered in the family home .
By whom ?
By her husband .
So say the police reports .
And her husband was shot to death by her own son .
Right in front of her daughter .
I intend to prove that none of the people I 've just described
were responsible for their actions .
Alan Russell was not a murderer . He was a victim .
One of many , as it turns out .
Victims of the supernatural force that resides in that mirror .
So why don 't we just end it right now and smash the goddamn thing ?
You really don 't remember , do you ?
( BOTH YELLING )
Remember what ?
Please , smash it , by all means .
Okay .
You know , I 've learned a lot about what happens to people when they can 't ...
can 't process something horrible .
The mind creates all kinds of protections to help them cope .
And once that belief 's taken root ,
the mind takes random information and forces it to support that narrative .
How many thousands of records did you have to pore through
to find 12 or 13 that support your case ?
Why did you put the stool down ?
Because I 'm trying to have a conversation with you .
Uh-huh . Only one person I know of was ever documented
trying to break the mirror .
Oliver Jeffries . 1971 .
A teacher at Manhattan 's Duhame Academy ,
where the mirror hung in the central lecture hall .
One morning he reportedly ran at the mirror with a fireplace poker ,
.. shouting about how it needed to be destroyed , ..
.. but he never struck a blow .
According to the students ,
he stood there quietly for almost a minute
before walking out of the hall and into traffic .
It 's clearly capable of defending itself , and ...
( WHISPERING )
... I think it just disarmed you .
You know why I didn 't smash the mirror , Kaylie ?
Besides you getting fired or charged with destruction of property ?
It isn 't mine to break .
No one can break your delusion for you .
You have to do it yourself .
Which leads me to my final precaution .
You 're looking at a 20-pound Danforth anchor .
Another 20 pounds added with barbells , attached to a modified ballast rail
and a spring pin lock connected to a mechanical kitchen timer .
No electricity , which is important , and we 're about ten seconds away .
If the timer is not manually reset every 30 minutes ,
that is , if no one is here to stop it ...
( TIMER TICKING )
( LOUD CLICK )
The mirror goes right there .
And the only thing to prevent that ..
.. from happening again is our continued survival .
You know why we don 't have to wait for it to come out and play ?
Because we 've got a loaded gun to its head .
And I expect it 'll be eager to defend itself .
( TIMER TICKING )
( SIGHS )
Aah !
( INDISTINCT WHISPERING )
FEMALE VOICE : ( WHISPERING ) It doesn 't hurt .
It doesn 't hurt .
It doesn 't hurt . It doesn 't hurt .
( MUSIC PLAYING ON TV )
- ( FOOTSTEPS APPROACH )
- ALAN : Hey guys ?
Come into my office for a second .
I thought I was pretty clear about you guys not messing around in here .
We don 't .
I don 't like it in here .
All right , well , what is this ?
We didn 't do that .
OK .
You know , I can hear you guys at night , messing around in here .
I was a kid once , too . I get it .
I know the move has been difficult .
This isn 't gonna happen anymore .
OK ?
And if you 're messing around with your mother 's plants ,
you 're gonna cut that out , too .
TIM : You know what dead plants are evidence of to me ?
Problems with the water supply and maybe a bad tank .
I seem to remember drinking out of a Brita filter .
Oliver Jeffries , dead plants in the classroom .
Tobin Capp , dead plants in the bedroom .
Garden service at Hill Trust Bank couldn 't understand
why they had dead plants all over the place .
Live plant .
( SCOFFS ) Live plants in the living room .
Live plants , plants that have life .
These are your rules , by the way .
Give it time .
It always starts with the low-hanging fruit .
It wasn 't just the plants it fed on , though .
There was another variable , too .
Dog ! ( WHISTLES )
Sorry , Dog .
( TIMER BUZZING )
Hydrate .
( DOG WHIMPERING )
Come on , boy .
Come on , Mason . Go fetch .
- Come on . Mason . - Go fetch .
Chase the stick . Chase the stick .
Come on . Go . Go .
( SIGHS )
I mean , the whole reason I got this thing
was because you were freaked out that we weren 't safe .
Said you saw somebody down here .
Yeah , but that doesn 't make me feel safer .
- Quite the opposite , actually . - ( ALAN SIGHS )
OK , I will lock it up , unloaded ,
where I 'm sure it 'll come in very handy in the case of an emergency .
Grotesque cow .
What did you just say to me ?
I didn 't say anything .
( INDISTINCT VOICES WHISPERING )
( MASON BARKING )
- ( GROWLS ) - Ow ! Jesus !
Alan !
- ( RATTLING DOOR ) - ALAN : I 'm working !
( INDISTINCT WHISPERING )
( ALAN MUTTERING )
Who are you talking to ?
Were you gonna do something about the damn barking ?
There 's something wrong with the dog , Alan . He bit me .
Are you OK ?
I 'm fine .
( SIGHS )
You know , you are just lost in your own world in here .
I 'm not lost in my own world ! I 'm working !
MARIE : I know that .
I 've supported that .
This isn 't you working hard .
ALAN : When you start your own business , it 's all on you .
I know that , Alan !
I have to do this !
ALAN : Guys . Listen , you got to do me a special favor today .
I have a golf session with a client .
And I 'm gonna need you to stay out of my office . OK ?
OK , Dad .
All right . I love you guys .
( WHIMPERING , BARKING )
( SIGHS )
Fine . You wanna go in , you 're going in .
Go shit on the CEO 's carpet .
( MASON WHIMPERING )
Shit .
Why can 't we let him out ?
Mom says Mason 's grounded .
( DOOR OPENS )
Hey , squirts . Why are you , uh ... ?
We have got to do something about that damn dog .
( SIGHS ) A hello would be nice .
He was a wrecking ball all day .
I had to lock him in your office .
Well , tether him up .
Where is he ?
Well , there 's the problem .
You 're remembering it wrong .
I promise . I 'm not remembering it wrong .
You are , though . Mason ...
Alice Carden 's Australian shepherd ,
Tobin Capp 's Dalmatian , the pets were never found . None of them .
Do you remember Mason toward the end ?
Vomiting , accidents all over the house .
My therapist had me research Parvo virus .
Oh , my God .
It 's a fatal canine illness ,
flagged by nausea , aggression , infected urine and stool ,
which , incidentally , can kill plants .
Mason was sick .
( RAPID PANTING )
All right , I 'll take him to the vet tomorrow .
ALAN : Bad news .
I don 't think we 're both coming home .
Mom , where 's Mason ?
Uh , he 's grounded .
Are you saying you remember it happening that way ?
- Are you really saying that ? - Why not ?
You 're wrong .
I saw Mom lock him in the office
and I sat outside that door all day , and nobody went in or out .
Have you ever heard of the fuzzy trace theory of human psychology ?
No . But I 'm gonna guess you have .
I 'm the star of a psychiatric article about it .
Our brains actually encode information as fuzzy traces .
More like a general meaning than an exact record .
This is horseshit , Tim .
Adults are more likely
to combine those traces into false memories .
You saw Mom put the dog in the office on a number of occasions .
My God , what did they do to you ?
Way before Dad forbade anyone else from going in the office .
Those traces fused with your memory of that day .
I feel sorry for you .
OK , what 's more likely ?
That you 're misremembering events from 11 years ago ,
or that the mirror eats dogs ?
Oh , look ! It 's Dog !
Give it some time .
( SWITCHING VIDEO TAPES )
A little time .
ALAN : There 's nothing going on here , woman !
You 're really losing it !
MARIE : I can hear you talking to someone , and it sounds like a woman .
ALAN : You know what , you 're crazy !
MARIE : I 'm not crazy !
I can hear you talking to someone .
ALAN : I mean , listen to yourself !
" I can hear you through the door . "
MARIE : Why would I make this up ?
I 'm not crazy !
ALAN : The water supply is poisoned ?
And we got a burglar ?
You 're losing your mind .
I 'm sorry that we woke you up .
Are you and Daddy fighting because of the woman in the office ?
You got to remember that woman .
You saw her too .
I convinced myself I saw a lot of things .
But what did we really see ?
Mom yelling at Dad in the middle of the night .
Mom said she heard voices , but it was probably just Dad on the phone .
( TIMER BUZZING )
Doesn 't explain the woman I saw through the window .
But when did you see her ?
The first time ?
We were playing in the yard .
Was Mom at home ?
Mom was always home .
Are you sure about that ?
Because I 'm not .
- Oh , shit . - Shit .
Get back . Get back .
( TYPING )
He was having an affair , saint that he was .
It was a bad marriage .
Look how it ended up .
- No . - Our father was a cheater ,
- and it drove our mother crazy . - Stop it .
He snapped and he killed her .
He was gonna do the same to us .
Oh , yeah . A bad marriage .
That explains how Mom had no teeth , no hair , no mind left ,
by the time she died .
Yeah , a bad marriage .
That explains those other people we both saw in the house that last night .
He was withdrawn , secretive .
All signs of an affair .
I had access to all of Mom and Dad 's stuff .
While you were getting brainwashed , I looked .
Not one credit card receipt , phone call , flower order .
Nothing to suggest an affair .
He was smart enough not to leave a trail .
- ( DOG BARKING ) - Quiet !
I talked to his friends and co-workers .
If there was another woman , she was a ghost .
Yeah , I agree , he was withdrawn , secretive , suspicious , sure .
All signs of an affair , fine .
I 'm not saying he wasn 't seduced .
It 's a matter of what seduced him .
( DOG WHIMPERING )
And things have been happening in here while we argue , you know .
You know the temperature in here has risen by three degrees ?
Three degrees .
Two people in a small space ,
lights burning , electrical equipment ...
Phone lines are probably down by now .
Why don 't you check ?
OK , then . Let 's have a look .
Dial tone .
Static ?
Look , Kaylie . You can deal with this . I did it .
You want to redeem the family name ?
You don 't need to do it for Mom and Dad .
You only need to do it for yourself .
Oh ...
They did a bang-up job on you in there , didn 't they ?
You were perfectly normal when they locked you up .
You had to go bat-shit to get out .
( DOG WHIMPERING , BARKING )
Mason , stop your goddamn whining !
You know what ?
That 's it . I 'm done .
I know I 'm supposed to wait around for you
to find your own way out of this .
But I 'm not gonna stand here and let you torture a dog .
What do you think you 're doing ?
Listen to it !
Stop it ! Stop it .
- ( SLAMS CAGE DOOR )
- ( BARKING )
No ! No ! Wait !
What ?
You didn 't need to do that .
Oh , yes , I did , Kaylie .
You 're sick .
Nothing you said would happen tonight has happened .
The plants are still alive , the mirror is just a mirror .
The only thing threatening that dog was you !
And it 's not your fault .
Like it wasn 't my fault .
I had help , and you were alone .
These kinds of problems are hard to overcome ,
but they 're nothing to be ashamed of .
They run in our family .
Kaylie , I 'm sorry .
Look ...
Let 's get out of here .
Go some place else and talk about how to move on .
( VOICE BREAKING ) Where can we go ?
Oh , Kaylie ...
Where ?
Let 's go turn off those cameras , disarm that anchor ...
and we can go anywhere you want .
Go talk to your fiancé , maybe .
He 'll want to help .
You know he will .
Kaylie ?
( BREATH TREMBLING )
There it is .
Ha !
Yes .
Yes !
Yes . Yes .
Yes . Yes !
I 'm now reviewing the tape of the last few minutes .
TIM : He was having an affair , saint that he was .
It was a bad marriage .
Look how it ended up .
Our father was a cheater , and it drove our mother crazy .
- Stop it . - He snapped and he killed her .
He was gonna do the same to us .
Yeah , a bad marriage .
That explains how Mom had no teeth , no hair , no mind left ,
by the time she died .
Yeah , a bad marriage .
That explains those other people we both saw in the house that last night .
I don 't remember doing that .
Do you ? You don 't .
The temperature in the room has increased another two degrees
to 78 degrees Fahrenheit ...
- but the alarms didn 't go off ... - My phone .
We 've lost the ficus and the blooming plants .
- My phone . - Which tells me that the dog
provided at least enough energy to bait the shark .
I 'd better call the doctor .
Tim . If you 're gonna make a phone call ,
you need to do it outside its radius of influence .
Otherwise there 's no way of knowing who you 're really talking to .
( PHONE RINGING )
Hello ? Hi . Yeah .
Everything 's fine now .
I 'm sorry about earlier .
I 'll talk to you in an hour .
50 / 50 that was even him .
We need to get out of this room for a while .
It must 've gotten more from the dog than I guessed .
Its radius of influence appears to be ... 30 feet ...
which means we 're still good to go in the kitchen ,
laundry room , garage , master bedroom ,
and the yard , front and back .
Oh , but I doubt for very long .
Tim ?
Tim !
VOICE RECORDING : Your call cannot be completed as dialed .
Your call cannot be completed as dialed .
Please check the number and dial again .
- ( PANTING ) - KAYLIE : Tim .
Tim .
How did I get back in here ?
What do you mean ?
You walked over here and you sat down .
I was outside .
No , you weren 't .
Did you think you were ?
Would you mind saying that on camera ?
( PANTING )
Hey . Hey !
It 's because you 're still here that I know we 're gonna win .
Do you hear me ?
Do you understand ?
( VACUUM CLEANER WHIRRING )
( VIDEO GAMES BEEPING )
( THUMPING )
( VACUUM CLEANER CONTINUES )
When 's Daddy coming home ?
I don 't know .
You don 't know when Daddy 's coming home ?
I don 't know where he is .
I know where he says he is .
Kaylie .
Tell me more about the woman in the office .
I haven 't seen her .
I have .
( MOUTHING )
( EXHALES )
When ?
Last night .
She wasn 't in the office .
She was on the stairs .
What was she doing ?
I didn 't look .
I was scared .
But I think she went back in the office .
I think she lives there .
You two go upstairs and play .
( HINGES CREAKING )
( SNIFFLES )
( YELLS )
( SNIFFLING )
( YELLING )
( LOUD WHOOSHING )
( FAINT WHISPERING )
( WHIMPERS )
( WHISPERING INCREASES )
( MARIE SCREAMING )
( SCREAMING CONTINUES )
Mom ?
Mom !
( MARIE WHIMPERING )
© P @ rM ! NdeR M @ nkÖÖ ™
©
© P @ rM ! NdeR
© P @ rM ! NdeR M @ nkÖÖ
Tim !
Mom !
( YELLING )
Go ! Go , Tim !
( BOTH SCREAMING )
- ( BOTH PANTING )
- ( POUNDING ON DOOR )
Mommy , stop !
Please stop , Mommy !
( POUNDING CONTINUES )
Marie ?
Hey ! Hey !
Baby ?
Sweetheart , you 're bleeding .
Hey , hey , hey !
( BOTH GRUNTING )
( DOOR CLICKS )
( SOBS )
( PANTING ) Sweetheart , you gotta go back in your room .
But , Mommy ...
Your mother 's fine .
She 's going to be all right .
Just , please , go back inside .
Shut the door , OK , baby ?
Fuck .
( DIALING )
Yeah , I have an emergency with my wife .
( INDISTINCT WHISPERING )
OVERLAPPING VOICES : Everything is fine .
- Is Mommy OK ? - Go to bed .
( CHAIN JINGLING )
( CRYING )
( DISTANT POUNDING )
Tim ?
Tim .
Snap out of it !
- ( TIMER BUZZING )
- Are you here ?
Are you here with me ?
Tim ?
Guys , your mother is very , very sick .
And , uh , she 's gonna need to stay in bed for a while , to rest up .
So she can get better .
But we don 't want you two bothering her .
We ?
So , Champ , Princess ...
we 're gonna have to stay clear of that room .
Is that understood ?
What does she have ?
Now ... ( CLEARS THROAT )
you are welcome to ...
hang out in here and play video games .
I thought you said we weren 't allowed in here .
( TIMER BUZZING )
Eat .
Come on , I need your help .
KAYLIE : Tim !
Tim , snap out of it !
( ECHOING ) Tim !
( FOOTSTEPS )
Is that for Mom ?
Tim ?
Nice .
( GLASS SPLINTERING )
( GASPS )
( BREATH SHUDDERING )
( SPITTING )
( GAGGING )
( WHIMPERING )
( GASPS )
- TIM : Kaylie ? - ( GASPS )
( EXHALES )
Maybe we should stay together .
( EXCLAIMING ) She still loves me !
( MUFFLED THUMPING )
I 'm hungry , Kaylie .
( SIGHS )
You need to go grocery shopping , Dad .
What 's that , Princess ?
- Food . - That 's on my list .
The TV is out .
What 's that , Princess ?
We need to call a doctor for Mom .
That 's on my list .
( LOW RUMBLING )
( HUFFS )
( INDISTINCT WHISPERING )
This is stupid .
I 'm gonna tell her we 're out of food .
- But Dad said ... - I don 't care what Dad said .
( TAKING DEEP BREATH )
( HINGES CREAKING )
Mom ?
( GASPS , SHRIEKS )
( GUTTURAL MOANING )
( SHRIEKING )
KAYLIE : She needs a doctor !
You told me she was sick , but she 's not ...
You know what your problem is ?
You don 't listen !
I told you not to go into our room , didn 't I ?
What do you do ?
You disobey me .
Why ?
You disobeyed me , so now you get grounded .
You and your snot-nosed little brother over there
are not to step foot outside of this house .
Now , get out of here .
KAYLIE : OK . Thank you .
Bye .
TIM : What did the doctor say ?
He said to have our father call .
Like the last one .
Exactly like the last one .
Same voice .
( KNOCKING ON DOOR )
Hi , Bob .
BOB : I 'm really sorry to hear that .
I hope she gets better soon .
ALAN : Thanks for that , Bob .
You know what ? I 'm just sorry she brought you all the way over here .
I mean , she 's ... you know , using her mother 's illness to act out .
Wait till she starts driving .
This is nothing .
Well , so sorry to bother you .
I hope Marie is up and about soon .
Thank you .
Hey , you know what ?
Give me a ring next week
and we 'll play the front nine at Arrowhead .
Great . We 'll do it .
- See ya . - Take care .
KAYLIE : Timbo .
We 're gonna have to get really , really brave .
( TIMER TICKING )
( PANTING )
Very clever .
- Tim ! - ( TIMER BUZZING )
( TIMER CLATTERING )
( ELECTRICITY CRACKLES )
( TOY GUN FIRING )
( EXHALES )
( LAMP BUZZING )
Kaylie ?
And we 've lost electric .
Predictable .
A dead plant .
It isn 't real .
Daddy ?
( SLOW TYPING )
Could you fix the lights ?
( TIM SCREAMING )
( HISSING )
( PANTING )
Nice tricks .
( GASPS )
MICHAEL 'S VOICE : Kaylie ...
( MICHAEL GASPS )
Oh , my God .
Do you see him ?
- ( PANTING )
- ( KAYLIE SNIFFLES )
( CELL PHONE RINGING )
Hello ?
MICHAEL : Just checking in , seeing how everything 's going .
I 'm fine .
OK , I guess I 'll talk to you in an hour .
Enjoyed the chat .
That 's a trick .
I didn 't kill him .
I couldn 't have .
The plate , it wasn 't real .
I didn 't kill him because the plate wasn 't real !
( SOBBING )
( PHONE CLATTERING )
Michael .
What did I do ? What did I do ?
TIM : Come on . We 're getting out of here .
Come on , let 's go .
Hello ?
I need police and an ambulance .
2705 Hawthorne .
OK , OK .
Help is coming . They 'll be here .
We 'll straighten all this out .
Kaylie , we 're OK .
We 're OK .
Michael , Michael , Michael .
When was the last time you reset the kitchen timer ?
I don 't know .
Your plan was solid .
We don 't have to do anything .
All we have to do is just sit here and wait .
No more than half an hour .
Your kill switch .
- You called for help ? - Yeah .
We 're done . It 's over .
We get to stand here and watch that thing die .
( BREATH SHUDDERING )
It 's a trick to get us back inside .
What if this is a trick to keep us standing there ?
- I called for help . - Call again .
MAN : 911 . What 's your emergency ?
Yeah , hi , I just called . 2705 Hawthorne .
You 're going to have to have your father call .
The doctor will be there tomorrow .
( DISTORTED ) Timbo ...
KAYLIE : No !
( PHONE CRUNCHES )
What do we do ?
We could do nothing . Just wait .
And watch ourselves get ...
We 're gonna have to get really , really brave .
( INDISTINCT WHISPERING )
He looked at the mirror and took out a gun .
We 're gonna have to smash it .
( WHISPERING ) That 's not real .
ALAN 'S VOICE : I thought I told you not to play around in here .
It 's not real .
( BOTH YELLING )
( WHIMPERING )
Shh !
( GLASS CRUNCHING )
( CHAIN RATTLING )
- Kaylie ? - ( GASPS )
Is he gone ?
He was never here .
It just herded us upstairs .
We made the right call outside .
It 's really trying to keep us away .
It 'll try harder .
We have to get downstairs
before that anchor swings .
You have to make sure he 's gone first .
He 's gone . I promise . See , he 's ...
( SHRIEKS )
( POUNDING ON DOOR )
( BOTH WHIMPERING )
( POUNDING CONTINUES )
( POUNDING CEASES )
We 've got to get downstairs .
She 's not gone .
- I 'm gonna open the door . - No !
I 'm gonna open the door .
If she 's not gone ...
I want you to run right down the stairs .
What are you gonna do ?
Don 't worry about that . Just run .
You ready ?
I 'm gonna open the door .
You run right down the stairs .
You trust me , right ?
I trust you .
One ... I love you .
Two ... Straight for the stairs .
Three .
- ( GRUNTING )
- ( BOTH SHRIEK )
( GROANING )
( PANTING )
( WHISPERING ) It 's not real .
Just a trick .
You 're gonna arrest me , Timbo ?
( LOUD GUNSHOT )
Timbo ?
Tim !
( FAINT WHISPERING )
( VOICE SHAKY ) Tim ?
( MOUTHING )
( SCREAMS )
( CRYING ) Mommy , please , no .
( SCREAMING )
© P @ rM ! NdeR M @ nkÖÖ ™
( GASPING , COUGHING )
( WHISPERING ) Kaylie ?
- Kaylie ? - ( GUNSHOT )
Mommy !
Come on , Tim !
( SCREAMS )
( GASPING SOFTLY )
( INDISTINCT WHISPERS OVERLAPPING )
( BOTH GRUNTING )
It won 't let us .
ALAN : I thought I told you not to play around in here .
No .
This isn 't you .
It is me .
( WHISPERS ECHOING )
I 've met my demons , and they are many .
WHISPERING VOICE : I 've seen ...
I 've seen the devil ...
WHISPERING VOICE : And he is ...
and he is me .
( YELLING )
Dad !
Let her go !
( GASPING )
Run .
No ! No !
Daddy !
( SOBBING )
Come on .
( BOTH WHIMPERING )
( TIMER BUZZING LOUDLY )
This isn 't real ! This isn 't real !
This isn 't real !
( BUZZING FADES )
Kaylie !
TIM : ( DISTANT ) Kaylie !
( SNIFFLING )
MARIE : Kaylie .
Mommy ?
( TICKING )
( WET THUDDING )
( FAINT GURGLING )
( KAYLIE GAGGING )
KAYLIE : Tim . Tim look at me .
I want you to promise me , that when we 're big and we 're strong ,
we will make this right .
( DISTANT SIRENS APPROACHING )
We have to kill that thing .
For Mom and Dad .
I promise .
( STAMMERING ) Kaylie ?
Kaylie ?
Kaylie ! Kaylie ! Kaylie !
( SIRENS GROWING LOUDER )
( INDISTINCT RADIO CHATTER )
He called it in ?
Yeah , he called 911 , and then he did this .
Where are you taking me ?
No , it wasn 't my fault !
- It was the mirror ! - Tim !
Wait ! Stop ! It wasn 't me !
It wasn 't me . It was the mirror !
It was the mirror !
Please ! Please ! You have to believe me !
It was the mirror ! It was the mirror !
Please !
Hey ! Hey !
KAYLIE : Don 't forget !
Don 't forget our promise !
Don 't forget .
( SIREN WAILING )
( WHIMPERING )
( RADIO CHATTER FADES )
( HEART BEATING )
©
© P @ rM ! NdeR
© P @ rM ! NdeR M @ nkÖÖ